[
    {
        "front": "できます ❘❘",
        "back": "be able to, can",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "あらいます ❘",
        "back": "wash",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひきます ❘",
        "back": "play (stringed instrument or piano, etc.)",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "うたいます ❘",
        "back": "sing",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "あつめます ❘❘",
        "back": "collect, gather",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "すてます ❘❘",
        "back": "throw away",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "かえます ❘❘",
        "back": "change, exchange",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "うんてんします ❘❘❘",
        "back": "drive",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "よやくします ❘❘❘",
        "back": "reserve, book",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "けんがくします ❘❘❘",
        "back": "visit some place for study",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "ピアノ",
        "back": "piano",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "メートル",
        "back": "meter",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "こくさい",
        "back": "international~",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "げんきん",
        "back": "Cash",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅみ",
        "back": "hobby",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "にっき",
        "back": "diary",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "おいのり",
        "back": "prayer (～します: pray)",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "かちょう",
        "back": "section chief",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぶちょう",
        "back": "department chief",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゃちょう",
        "back": "president of a company",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "どうぶつ",
        "back": "animal",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "うま",
        "back": "horse",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "へえ。。。",
        "back": "Really! (Used when expressing surprise)",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "それわ おもしろいですね",
        "back": "That must be interesting.",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "なかなか",
        "back": "not easily (Used with negatives)",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぼくじょう",
        "back": "cattle farm, animal farm",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほんとうですか",
        "back": "Really?",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぜひ",
        "back": "definitely, by all means",
        "chapter": "N5 C18"
    }
]